{
    "subject": "resource/Hairspray_(2007_film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_about_television",
    "human_readable": "Hairspray (2007 film) is about television.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8542760610580444,
            "question": "Who directed the film Hairspray (2007)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7812445759773254,
            "question": "What is the main theme of the film Hairspray (2007)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.562086284160614,
            "question": "What year was the film Hairspray released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.425398051738739,
            "question": "Who are some of the main characters in the film Hairspray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41164419054985046,
            "question": "Is the film Hairspray a musical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3645150363445282,
            "question": "Where was Hairspray filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3369584083557129,
            "question": "What is the overall message conveyed by the film Hairspray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28110063076019287,
            "question": "Is Hairspray based on a true story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.262327641248703,
            "question": "What decade does the story of Hairspray take place in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18178756535053253,
            "question": "What are some important social issues explored in Hairspray?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hairspray (2007 film) is about television.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6128_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What decade does the story of Hairspray take place in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6128_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Hairspray based on a true story?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6128_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall message conveyed by the film Hairspray?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6128_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6128_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6128_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6128_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6128_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6128_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6128_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6128_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6128_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6128_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6128_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention anything about a connection between the movie Hairspray and television. The closest related information is that there was a live television adaptation of Hairspray, but this does not mean that the original film is about television."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Hairspray (2007 film) is about television.\" Specifically, they mention that the film takes place during a time of social change and tackles themes of racial integration and body positivity. Additionally, it is noted that the 2016 adaptation was a live television event, suggesting that the original 2007 film also involves elements related to television, as it likely forms part of the narrative or setting in Baltimore during that era."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Hairspray (2007 film) does not revolve around television. It follows the story of a friendly teen, Tracy Turnblad, who aspires to dance on a local TV show in Baltimore during the 1960s, but the main plot focuses on racial and gender discrimination, self-acceptance, and body positivity.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text describes Hairspray as a musical set in Baltimore during the 1960s, focusing on a teenager named Tracy Turnblad and themes of racial and social integration. There's no mention of it being about television.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The information provided indicates that the 2007 film Hairspray has a live television adaptation, but it does not suggest that the original story itself is about television. The plot of the movie takes place in Baltimore during the 1960s and follows Tracy Turnblad's journey as she becomes a regular on a local dance show.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}